basically we're just going to circle
yeah your words taking you back it's
just one word I just want to start with
everyone just like one word whatever's
there for you just just as you bring
your attention to her just one word if
it's there no I'll go first
Wonder
keep going
I notice there's moisture coming up to
your eyes like two or three different
occasions it seems like there was why
they're happening there but it's what is
the weather do you feel like mmm like
I'm sitting here hearing these words
coming from other points of
consciousness and it's like seeing the
contrast between my own thoughts with
myself and so it just caused me to feel
loved in a way but I don't get to myself
it just
so some of the emotion came up when you
felt the contrast is that what I heard
between like what you would think or
what you would maybe say a or implicitly
or explicitly and what you heard from
them something about that contrast like
broke up in love or had you feel loved
all the words I have with myself to try
to contain this image that I want to
make hold on to so so it's like you felt
sadness you felt love and you felt loved
and then at the same time or closely
after that there's this sadness for the
lack of love for myself so yeah so I'm
feeling excited like I I'm really
excited to like feel that bottom line
like what it feels cross over that that
like structure of myself into like who I
really am and I think I've been I've
been searching for that my whole life
this struck me wanting this or grasping
of wanting to exist seer like the the
twinkle in your eye no like a like
little background smile that's see this
occurred to me through almost like a
through line through everything that
you've been talking so you've been
talking just made sense to me it's
almost it's almost like it's it's
interesting my experience is almost like
almost like you feel like you're getting
away with something right great it's
like that this is there's this joy you
know like what I'm hearing you say is
like you're all you talking about things
like kind of yeah I feel like what I've
considered myself to be
going to annihilate it right in fact I
kind of want to mm-hmm right and God it
sucks
but I feel loved and like whoa this is
intense but I would do it I I'd pay for
it I'd pay to do it again or something
totally totally like that there's just a
pre reflective that's the thing I want
to get close to I know this with you
yeah yes I could get this sense of just
like almost like that there's something
in the background that's just listening
for like listening I don't know for like
that sense of like where you're in a
crowd you're going to be in this crowded
chaotic place and if you hear your own
name there's like like all the animals
Hashmi like all like something's
listening steps that when I hear it-it's
but I realize like oh I've been
listening the whole time for something I
just get that sense with you yeah I'm
enjoying that reflection I'm thinking
about being present with that like maybe
that's who I really am
just like I just wanted I want to create
space for the awesomeness of it I had
this sense that we were actually like
when you talked about going over the
cliff
I had a sense I think we're all ready I
think we are falling
it wasn't sure and it's different than I
expected expected to kind of like fumble
through like more of my darkness but
like what I'm experiencing right now is
my light what I'm experiencing right now
is my life so like there's a sliver of
my like being that's like I just got a
glimpse of and like there's all this
stuff that was like in my way of like
seeing truth and like who I am and like
it's still holding all this crazy
to like all one still I just hope
there's a little bit
thank you I'd get I've gotten curious
about every single experience of my life
like I never ignored anything
feels like it's always been there and
it's never abandoned me
it feels good to have like that
untouchable of speakable like that with
something other than something you have
some level of like the weave and you
just comprehend it it's like really
complex
I feel like I could see here with you
for like ever
lately it's how they hit the die to get
here I don't think I've ever heard
anyone say that to me
and I get I get to know that I don't
have to die in order to like the
understand like on this really deep real
level for me that like probably seems
really unreal the most people unless you
do like massive amounts of acid or
something
here it is I didn't think that people
are like I didn't know I mean this skill
is really unique you don't find it in
the world you know and like that's why
I'm here
like that's accessing areas that you
just didn't know this that's amazing
like I feel like it like rewires the
brain like it does this like real
physiological change like that moment of
like getting that I don't have to die to
be met in this way that felt unbeatable
changed every soul in my body like I
have new eyes
I feel like I'm sitting and listening to
the prophet of the profane you are
conscious of any sort of extra need to
be like more consistently getting her
world yeah because it was like it like
you kept drawing like bigger and more
personal dimensions at the same time
that like I actually needed to I needed
to get it to be able to like be to stay
up with the conversation basically and
it also occurred to me like and would
seem to come at the end I said that's
what was one of her deepest needs
you just kept yeah that act alone is
what made me feel like love that he like
because it was kind of hard to
comprehend so you just kept going and
like that's what me